<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">

  <title><![CDATA[Life ,The Universe and The Thing]]></title>
  <link href="http://ace03uec.github.io/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  <link href="http://ace03uec.github.io/"/>
  <updated>2013-08-29T08:36:33+05:30</updated>
  <id>http://ace03uec.github.io/</id>
  <author>
    <name><![CDATA[Giridaran M.]]></name>
    <email><![CDATA[giridar123@gmail.com]]></email>
  </author>
  <generator uri="http://octopress.org/">Octopress</generator>

  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[elementary things to iron out]]></title>
    <link href="http://ace03uec.github.io/blog/2013/08/27/elementary-things-to-iron-out/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-27T21:16:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://ace03uec.github.io/blog/2013/08/27/elementary-things-to-iron-out</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h1>Elementary OS</h1>

<p>With the number of Ubuntu clones increasing day by day and now with them being stable and visually stunning, ElementaryOS stands out.
Its sleek and the title and menu bars in pantheon have just the right amount of gloss that works for me.(To Mint lovers out there, too shiny for my tastes, sorry!)
Though now that i have used it for more than 2 weeks,there are some problems that need to be ironed out.</p>

<ul>
<li><h1>Files</h1>

<p>The biggest issue i seem to be having is that Files seems to have some trouble loading some particular filesystems. This issue seems to revolve around USB disks and drives with low space. Mounting harddisks, both internal and external seems to be no issue.</p></li>
<li><h1>nm-applet</h1>

<p>Another quirky thing is that nm-applet does not automatically connect or even search for networks when booted. An easy fix is to choose connect to a hidden network, when it begins searches as well if you give a bogus hidden network name.Still have to find a permanent fix for this though.</p></li>
<li><h1>Terminal</h1>

<p>To other ruby, octopress users out there: If you have any issue in using rvm in pantheon-teminal Just add the .bash_profile file to your .bashrc (Copy the syntax for the .bash_aliases file). This issue is simply because rvm uses a login shell to manage profiles within different folders.<a href="http://www.linuxfromscratch.org/blfs/view/6.3/postlfs/profile.html">This</a> page has some great info regarding the same.</p></li>
</ul>

]]></content>
  </entry>
  
  <entry>
    <title type="html"><![CDATA[Hello Octopress]]></title>
    <link href="http://ace03uec.github.io/blog/2013/08/19/hello-octopress/"/>
    <updated>2013-08-19T16:02:00+05:30</updated>
    <id>http://ace03uec.github.io/blog/2013/08/19/hello-octopress</id>
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<h3>Hello World</h3>

<p>This post has been some time coming. So I won&rsquo;t keep this too long.</p>

<p>This Blog is hosted on github-pages by <a href="http://octopress.org/" title="Octopress">Octopress</a>, The Blogging platform for hackers.
Settingup did take some time, but then again that was becuase of the problems with pantheon.
That reminds me, Been using <a href="http://elementaryos.org/" title="Elementary OS">elementaryOS</a> &ldquo;luna&rdquo; for about a week now,And i must say, WOW.
Not to say i didn&rsquo;t have my fair share of set up worries, but then again that&rsquo;s what i love about the whole experience.</p>
]]></content>
  </entry>
  
</feed>
